<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AndroidDevLayoutExercise</string>
    <string name="textDetailDefaultString">Phone details...</string>
    <string name="phoneNameDefaultString">Phone name</string>
    <string name="backButtonName">Back</string>
    <string name="androidDetailsText">Android is a mobile operating system developed by Google, based on the Linux kernel and designed primarily for touchscreen mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets. Android s user interface is mainly based on direct manipulation, using touch gestures that loosely correspond to real-world actions, such as swiping, tapping and pinching, to manipulate on-screen objects, along with a virtual keyboard for text input.</string>
    <string name="iPhoneDetailsText">iOS (formerly iPhone OS) is a mobile operating system created and developed by Apple Inc. exclusively for its hardware. It is the operating system that presently powers many of the company s mobile devices, including the iPhone, iPad, and iPod touch. It is the second most popular mobile operating system globally after Android by sales. iPad tablets are also the second most popular, by sales, against Android since 2013, when Android tablet sales increased by 127%.</string>
    <string name="windowsMobileDetailsText">Windows Mobile is a family of mobile operating systems developed by Microsoft for smartphones and Pocket PCs. Its origins dated back to Windows CE in 1996, though Windows Mobile itself first appeared in 2000 as PocketPC 2000. It was renamed "Windows Mobile" in 2003, at which point it came in several versions (similar to the desktop versions of Windows) and was aimed at business and enterprise consumers.</string>
    <string name="blackberryDetailsText">BlackBerry OS is a proprietary mobile operating system developed by BlackBerry Limited for its BlackBerry line of smartphone handheld devices. The operating system provides multitasking and supports specialized input devices that have been adopted by BlackBerry for use in its handhelds, particularly the trackwheel, trackball, and most recently, the trackpad and touchscreen.</string>
    <string name="webOSDetailsText">WebOS, also known as Open WebOS or LG WebOS, (previously known as HP WebOS and Palm WebOS, stylized as webOS) is a Linux kernel-based multitask operating system for smart devices like TVs and smartwatches. It was formerly a mobile operating system. Initially developed by Palm (which was acquired by Hewlett-Packard), HP made the platform open source, at which point it became Open WebOS. The operating system was later sold to LG Electronics.</string>
    <string name="ubuntuDetailsText">Ubuntu Mobile Internet Device Edition was an Ubuntu distribution planned to run on the Intel Mobile Internet Device platform, x86 mobile computers based on the Intel Atom processor. It was planned to use the GNOME framework Hildon as the basis for its GUI. Equipment producers would have been able to customize their distributions, including options such as Flash, Java, or custom interfaces. Ubuntu Mobile has stopped development in 2009 and the successor Ubuntu for phones was announced on January 2, 2013.</string>
</resources>
